authorsure.com 2019-01-09

# Privacy

The AuthorSure.com website will collect personal details that you provide to us for the purposes of providing you with services and/or information. In providing such services and/or information to you we will only use your data in accordance with the terms of the following statement.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, please contact us.

### Information Collection and Use

AuthorSure.com owns any information collected via this site. We will not sell, share, nor rent this information to any other party. AuthorSure.com collects information from our visitors at several different points on our website. This can happen because you’ve completed a contact form, or because you’ve signed up to our list to receive AuthorSure tutorials.

### We Employ Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user’s activity on our website. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. >

### External Links

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that AuthorSure.com are not responsible for the privacy policies of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this web site.

## How to Contact Us

Questions about this statement or about our handling of your information may be sent by email to [privacy@purpleparasol.com](mailto:privacy@purpleparasol.com), or by post to Purple Parasol Privacy Office, PO Box 85, Hatherleigh, Okehampton, Devon, EX20 3WH UK. 

#### About 

Liz is part of DiyWebmastery - she creates WordPress sites for clients, and teaches WordPress SEO to her one on one WordPress coaching students.
